（1981年建 回音谷农场）
早上好 亲爱的
Good morning, sweetheart.
我今天早上不得不很早离开去送一些马鞍
I had to leave super early thismorning to drop off some saddles.
希望没吵醒你
I hope I didn't wake you.
雨停了的话能麻烦你带马去外面走走吗
Could you take the horses outif it stopped raining?
我大概一小时后到家
I'll be back home in about an hour.
走吧 我们出去
Come on. Let's go.
（帕蒂 手机）
我在想 我们这周末不出去了 怎么样
I was thinking,let's stay home this weekend, huh?
把一直拖延不做的待办事项完成了
Catch up on that to-do listwe keep putting off?
我保证会修卧室天花板的那条裂缝
I promise I'll fix thatcrack in the bedroom ceiling.
嘿 我只想说 昨晚的事 很抱歉
Hey, I just wanted to saysorry about last night.
我喝醉了 口无遮拦
I was just drunk and being insensitive.
总之 我半小时后会到家
Anyway, I'm back home in half an hour
我会对你发动亲吻战术 直到你原谅我
and I'm going to shower youwith kisses until you forgive me.
凯特 不好意思
Kate. I'm sorry.
-我不是故意吓你的-没事 抱歉
- I didn't mean to scare you.- No. Sorry.
让我先拿出
Let me just take out my…
结论是什么
What's the verdict?
你还是和我一起去看看吧 你还是和我一起去看看吧
You wanna come and have a look with me? You wanna come and have a look with me?
我去吗 有必要
I don't know. Do I?
行 走吧 库珀
Okay. Come on, Coop.
看到那些凹陷处吗 椽子随时都可能坍塌
You see the dips?Those rafters could collapse any day now.
塌了麻烦就大了
Then you've got a real mess on your hands.
换掉要多少钱
How much to replace it?
如果你还是用沥青瓦那大概要九千美元左右
Well, if you stick with the shingles,you're looking at around $9,000.
好的 我考虑一下再回复你
Okay, let me think on itand I'll get back to you.
你慢慢考虑
No rush.
（2021年百大律师）
-凯特 早安-嗨
- Morning, Kate.- Hi.
汉娜 你怎么还没换衣服
Hannah, why are you not dressed?
你能礼貌一点 和凯特打声招呼吗 你能礼貌一点 和凯特打声招呼吗
Could you be a little politeand say hi to Kate? Could you be a little politeand say hi to Kate?
嗨 凯特
Hi, Kate.
嗨 亲爱的
Hi, sweetheart.
理查德 亲爱的 凯特又来了
Richard, honey, Kate's here again.
我在办公室
I'm back in my office.
真抱歉 我得帮小家伙准备出门了
Sorry, I gotta get this little one ready.
-你要不要直接进去 -是 好的 谢谢
- Do you wanna just go on in?- Yeah, of course. Thank you.
来吧 宝宝 我们得快点了
Come on, sweetie. We got to hustle.
我来了 天 妈妈
I'm coming, I'm coming. Geez, Mom.
-早上好-嗨
- Good morning.- Hey.
进来吧
Come in.
我在找一份案卷
I'm trying to find a brief.
我雇了个新助理 不太合得来
I hired a new assistant,and it's not working out.
我不知道东西都放哪了
I don't know where the hell anything is.
请坐吧
Please, sit.
谢谢
Thanks.
好 是这个
Yeah, this is good.
你发信息说要谈屋顶的事 对吗
So, your message said you neededto discuss the roof. Is that right?
对
Yeah…
兰迪来看了看 很不幸 我们需要换个屋顶
Randy came out to take a lookand unfortunately, we need a new one.
-不意外啊-我知道
- Well, not surprised.- I know. I know.
我还以为能再撑两年的
I thought that we had two years,
-至少-多少钱 -至少-多少钱
- you know, at least.- How much? - you know, at least.- How much?
多少钱
How much?
九千
9,000.
九千 这个笑话开始不好笑了
9,000. This is turning into a bad joke.
不 但新屋顶保证能用十年
No, but it's guaranteed to last ten years.
他说了 至少十年
He said at least ten years.
你知道 我在俱乐部遇到凯西杜蒙
You know,I ran into Kathy Dumont at the club.
她说过去六个月你取消了她女儿的马术课
She said you'd canceled her daughter'sriding lessons for the past six months.
希拉里斯塔福德也说了同样的话
Hilary Stafford told me the same thing.
听着 你失去了帕蒂 我很难过
Look, I'm sorry you lost Patty,
但我不能继续给失败的生意投钱了
but I can't continue to pour moneyinto a failing business,
尤其是我们已经不是夫妻了
especially 'causewe're not married anymore.
我一开始就不想要那个农场
And I never wanted that farmin the first place.
如果你经营不下去了 就必须卖了它
If you can't make it work,you're gonna have to sell it.
拜拜 理查德
Bye, Richard.
拜拜 爸爸
Bye, Dad.
拜拜 见到你们很开心
Bye. Nice to see you guys.
-玩得开心点-我要迟到了 走吧
- Have fun.- I'm late. Let's go.
谢谢
Thanks.
我猜克莱尔没有联系你
I'm guessing youhaven't heard from Claire.
她上周来过这里
She showed up here last week.
凌晨3点 砰砰拍前门
Three o'clock in the morningand she's pounding on the front door.
她想要什么 我
What did she want? I me--
她还能要什么 钱
What does she always want? Money.
你对她有求必应 只会惯坏她
And it doesn't help that youcontinue to give her anything she wants.
她是我们的女儿 理查德
She's our daughter, Richard.
-什 -我们做过承诺
- What--- We made promises
见律师的时候 记得吗
when we sat down with the counselor,do you remember?
-我们都发誓 不会助 -是 你知道我努力了的
- We both made pledges not to enable--- Yes. You know I tried.
-你知道我努力 -你从没努力过 凯特
- You know I tried--- You never tried, Kate.
她去找你 给你一个微笑然后你就心甘情愿假装一切安好
She'll show up and give you that smile andyou'll gladly pretend everything is fine.
一切都不好 我们的女儿病得很重
It's not fine. Our daughter is very sick.
它只在你回家时叫
He only barks when you come home.
你给它喂得够吗
Are you feeding him enough?
-它都要把我的手吞进去了-少来 别这么说 它好好的
- He's about to eat my hand off.- Stop it. Come on, he's fine.
我好想你
I missed you so much.
我更想你
I missed you more.
妈 你头发怎么回事
What is going on with your hair, Mom?
我还想问你呢
I could ask you the same thing.
好吧 我打电话给你订个预约
Okay, well, I'm gonna calland make you an appointment.
你真的需要重新开始好好照顾自己了
You really need to starttaking care of yourself again.
你为什么不回我电话
Why didn't you call me back?
说来话长 说来话长
It's a long story. It's a long story.
对了 能用一下你的iPad吗 我想查短信
Speaking of, can I have your iPadso I can check my messages?
好的 你去哪了
Okay. Where were you?
莱恩有几个朋友在杜伊海滩租了一个房子
A couple of Ryan's friendsrented a house down in Dewey Beach.
你没收到我的短信
You didn't get my messages?
没有 我手机没电了
No, my phone died.
手机是新买的
We just bought it.
-就坏了 -被莱恩扔进海里了
- It broke already?- Ryan threw it into the ocean
像情急下一记长传球
like a Hail Mary pass. Like…
噗的一声入水 变鱼食
Splash. Fish food.
他为什么要扔
Why did he do that?
因为他是个混蛋
'Cause he is a fuckface.
别担心 我已出了气
Don't worry, I got him back.
我走前去他的衣柜拿走了他所有东西
Before I left, I went into his closet,and I gathered up all his shit
从21桥上扔下去
and I threw it over the 21st bridge.
他现在大概正慌呢
He is probably freakingthe fuck out right now.
天啊 真的
Oh, my God. He totally is.
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
（我认真的 这不好笑我的东西到底在哪 ）
噢 克莱尔 这样不对
Oh, Claire, come on.
当着女友面给贱货们发老二照片
Well, that's what happenswhen you send dick pics to skanks
就别怪我这么做
in front of your girlfriend.
也许你应该和他分手
Maybe you should break up with him.
我会的 这就去分
I am going. Sprinting.
但在那之前 我需要
But first, I need…
我需要一部手机 我们能去威瑞森店吗
I need a phone, so can we go to Verizon?
好 我把马关进去 然后我们开车过去
Yeah, let me put the horses inand we can then ride over.
你饿吗 要吃烤芝士三文治吗
You hungry? You want a grilled cheese?
我饿死了
I am starving.
那
So…
你感觉还好吗
are you feeling good?
我没碰毒品 妈 我没事
I'm clean, Mom. I'm good.
你回来真好
So happy you're here.
你是不是吃醋啦
Are you getting jealous?Are you getting jealous?
明天想去玛什湖游泳吗
You wanna go for a swim tomorrowdown at Marsh Lake?
对你有好处的
It'll be good for you.
是 再看吧
Yeah, well, we'll see.
记得我小时候坚信湖里住着一个鬼吗
Remember when I was little, and I wasconvinced a ghost lived in the lake?
是 我当然记得 是 我当然记得
Yes, of course I remember that. Yes, of course I remember that.
你叫她爱丽儿 对吧
You called her Ariel, right?
-不对 欧若拉-欧若拉
- No, Aurora.- Aurora.
玛什溪湖之鬼魂
The ghost of Marsh Creek Lake.
好吓人
So scary.
没事 我去
No, I got it.
我东西呢
Where's my stuff?
天啊 你的脸怎么了
Oh, my God. What happened to your face?
别闹我 克莱尔 我知道是你拿走的
Stop fucking around, Claire.I know you took it.
莱恩 我不知道你在说什么
Ryan, I don't knowwhat you're talking about.
你知道我现在因为你惹了多大麻烦吗
Do you have any idea how much fuckingtrouble I'm in right now because of you?
我包里有半公斤货
There was a half a fucking kilo in my bag.
我告诉杰基说被你偷走了
Well, I told Jackie that you stole it.
-如果你不还回来 -什么
- So if you don't give it back…- What?
-你告诉杰基了 -他就会来找你
- You told Jackie?- …he's gonna come looking for you.
莱恩 你这人到底有什么毛病
Ryan,what the fuck is the matter with you?
你为什么要这样对我
Why the fuck would you do that to me?
因为我要吓死了 就这个原因
Because I'm fucking scared, that's why.
-你知道杰基的性格-莱恩 别告诉他我住在哪
- You know what Jackie's like.- Ryan, do not tell him where I live.
别告诉杰基我住在哪
Do not tell Jackie where I fucking live!
嘿
Hey.
嘿 你们还好吗
Hey, everything okay here?
我要出门
I'm going out.
去哪
Go where?
你要去哪
Where are you going?
亲爱的 你没事吧
Honey? You okay?
克莱尔
Claire?
Claire? Claire?
克莱尔
Claire.
站起来 来 站起来
Stand up for me. Come on, stand up for me.
很好 很好
There you go. There you go.
好的 很好
Okay. There you go.
克莱尔
Claire.
亲爱的 我要和你谈谈昨晚
Honey, I need to talk to youabout last night.
我下水游游 我下水游游
I'm gonna go take a dip. I'm gonna go take a dip.
你不能一直逃避这事
You can't keep avoiding this.
好的
Okay.
已经第15趟了 我手臂都要掉了
Trip number 15.I think my arms are gonna fall off.
我还记得这种日子
I remember those days.
请告诉我以后会轻松点
Tell me it gets easier.
噢 老天 不会 你等着瞧吧
Oh, God, no. Just you wait.
我开玩笑的
I'm just kidding.
每一天都是上天给的礼物
Every day is a gift.
好了 你们要看我前空翻还是后空翻
Okay, do you guys want me todo a front flip or a backflip?
后空翻
Backflip!
你们必须保证自己不会尝试这么做
You guys have to promise meyou're not gonna try this.
拉钩发誓好吗
You have to pinkie promise, okay?
让我看到你们每个人
Let me see all of you.
-我们拉钩发誓-你没拉钩
- We pinkie promise.- That's not a pinkie!
-有呀-快跳
- Yes it is.- Now, go!
好
Okay!
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
-嘿-嘿
- Hey.- Hey.
那天我电脑上跳出一个广告
You know, an ad popped upon my computer the other day
是切斯特社区大学的
from Chester Community College.
妈 电脑上不会随便跳出广告
Mom, an ad doesn't justpop up on your computer.
是因为你搜过
It's there 'cause you searched for it.
为什么会跳出来不重要
Well, it doesn't matter how it got there.
重要的是那所大学有创意写作课程
What matters is that theyoffer creative writing classes.
什么意思
Why does that matter?
因为你该考虑回去读书 因为你该考虑回去读书
Well, because you shouldthink about going back to school. Well, because you shouldthink about going back to school.
你很擅长写作
And you're a great writer.
我写了什么让你觉得我很擅长写作
What have I written that makesyou think I'm such a great writer?
你写了那个短篇故事
That short story you wrote
关于在动物园弄丢孩子的母亲的
about the motherwho loses her child at the zoo.
你觉得那个故事在讲什么
What do you think it was about?
我觉得 在我看来
I think that, for me…
它讲的是后悔
it was about regret.
我的意图不是这样
That's not what I intended it to be about.
看来那个故事也失败了 和我的人生一样
So I guess it was a failure,just like the rest of my life.
我很不喜欢你说这样的话
You know, I hate itwhen you say things like that.
你好 甜心
Hello, sweetheart.
一切可好
How you doing?
我不知道你是在这么偏远的地方长大的
I didn't realize you grew upall the way out here.
天啊 马匹和绿草
Man, horses and green grass…
美不胜收
It's beautiful.
和你一样
Just like you.
杰基 你是怎么找到我的
How'd you find me out here, Jackie?
嘿
Hey.
来吧
Come on.
要命
Man.
其实 我真的想不明白你看上了他哪点
You know, for the life of meI do not understand what you see in him,
因为我注意到你是怎么看我的
'cause I see the way you look at me.
我没怎么看你 杰基
I don't look at you any way, Jackie.
没有吗
No?
没有
No.
我的货呢
Where's my shit?
不在我这里
I don't have it.
不在你这里
You don't have it?
我不小心扔了 对不起
I threw it away by mistake and I'm sorry.
我不知道里面有你的货 杰基
I didn't knowyour shit was inside, Jackie.
-我不知道-该死的蠢婊子
- I didn't know.- Fucking dumb bitch.
你有什么毛病 你做了什么
The fuck's wrong with you?What'd you fucking do?
嘿 别碰她
Hey! Leave her alone.
什么
What?
你刚说什么
What'd you say?
什么
What?
该死
Fuck!
-你想去哪 过来-杰基
- Where you going? Come here.- Jackie.
过来
Come here.
过来 怎样
Come here. What? What?
不 不要紧
No, no, it's okay.
抱歉 我不是故意下手那么重的
Sorry, I didn't mean to hit you that hard.
深呼吸 慢慢地深呼吸
Just breathe.You just gotta breathe nice and slow.
慢慢地深呼吸 你没事
Breathe nice and slow. You're all right.
嘿 放开她
Hey! Get away from her!
你离她远点
Get the hell off of her.
你还好吗
You okay?
来
Come on.
这是怎么回事
What's going on here?
我真的很抱歉 盖瑞特森太太
I'm really sorry, Ms. Garretson.
嘿 你一定是克莱尔的妈妈
Hey, you must be Claire's mom.
我刚才只是在感叹这一区景色优美
I was just commentating onhow beautiful it is out here.
-马儿 -你是谁
- The horses--- Who are you?
我是你女儿的好朋友
I'm a close friend of your daughter's.
很可惜 她
Unfortunately, she…
听着 她背叛了我的信任拿走了不属于她的东西
Look, she betrayed my trust, and she tooksomething that didn't belong to her--
她没有偷东西
She didn't steal it.
-她是扔掉了-你闭嘴
- She threw it away.- Shut up.
这导致我和一些人的关系很紧张
And it's put me in a verybad spot with some people
而那些人我并不太想惹
I'd prefer not to be in a bad spot with.
妈 你离他远点 他是疯子
Stay away from him, Mom! He's crazy!
克莱尔 你怎么这样说
Claire, why would you say that
-你的好朋友 -嘿
- about a close friend?- Hey!
-妈 他不是我朋友-你必须离开 否则
- He's not my friend, Mom!- You need to leave or I'm…
我要报警了
I'm gonna call the police.
好的 但我们把话说清楚吧
Okay, but just so we're all clear,
你的毒虫女儿有两个选择
your junkie daughter has two choices.
物归原主 或者把钱还清 物归原主 或者把钱还清
Give it back, or she can pay me my money. Give it back, or she can pay me my money.
离开这里
Get out of here.
走
Come on.
你这废
You fucking…
拜拜 克莱尔
Bye, Claire!
那是谁
Who the hell was that?
你记得我说我把莱恩的东西从桥上扔下去吗
Remember when I said I threwRyan's stuff off the bridge?
-里面有些东西-你是说有毒品
- Well, there was something inside.- You mean there were drugs inside.
我当时不知道 妈
I didn't know it then, Mom.
真的 我扔下去的时候不知道
Honestly, I didn't knowwhen I threw it over.
那个人现在知道我们的住址克莱尔 要是他回来怎么办
That man knows where we live now, Claire.What if he comes back?
-他不会的-你也无法确定啊
- He won't.- No, you don't know that.
好吧 我不会允许他来的 妈
Okay, I won't let him, Mom.
克莱尔 这孩子
Goddamn it, Claire.
认真的
Really?
妈
Mom.
妈 听我解释
Mom, let me explain.
妈
Mom.
Mom!
他为什么在这里
What's he doing here?
我以为你要逃亡了
I thought you were running.
莱恩是因为我才惹祸上身的 莱恩是因为我才惹祸上身的
Ryan's in trouble because of me, Ryan's in trouble because of me,
他希望我来这里 向你道歉
and he wanted me to come hereand apologize to you
-因为我 杰基才找来这里-我才不在乎
- for bringing Jackie here earlier.- I don't give a shit.
我只要他离开
I just want him gone.
所以我们正要离开我们会在外面露营几天
Well, that's why we're leaving.We're gonna camp out for a few days.
你是说你们会吸几天
You mean you're gonna use for a few days?
不 妈 我们会去露营几天
No, Mom, we're gonna camp outfor a few days.
好吧
Okay.
带上这个
Here, take this.
纳洛酮 这样吧
Narcan. You know what?
全都带上
Take all of 'em
以防你又吸毒过量
in case you OD again.
妈 我需要一点钱
Mom, I need some money.
克莱尔 你就 走吧
Claire, just… just leave.
妈 我会走的 我只需要一点钱用来买食物和生活用品
Mom, I am leaving. I just needsome money for food and supplies.
食物和生活用品 你把我当傻子
Food and supplies?Do you think I'm that stupid?
莱恩因为我才惹祸的 妈
Ryan is in trouble because of me, Mom.
-我不会给你钱的-这次是认真的
- I'm not giving you money.- It's serious this time.
-我向你父亲保证过 -天啊 又是那个保证
- I made a pledge to your father--- Oh, my God. The pledge!
该死的保证 你和爸那个什么鬼保证
The fucking pledge!You and Dad and your fucking pledge!
我保证会对女儿不管不顾
I pledge allegianceto neglect my daughter,
-一点也不在乎她-一点不在乎 这话你能说出口
- not give a flying fuck about her!- Not give a fuck, really?
-妈 我需要一点钱 妈-我没有钱 -妈 我需要一点钱 妈-我没有钱
- Mom, I need some money. Mom!- I don't have any money! - Mom, I need some money. Mom!- I don't have any money!
钱都花光了 为了让你变好 但显然并没用
It's all gone towards getting you betterand clearly it hasn't worked.
妈 你要去哪
Mom, where are you going?
妈 我遇到麻烦了
Mom, I am in trouble.
我需要钱 妈
I need money, Mom.
妈 帮帮我
Mom, I need help.
妈 给我一点钱
Mom, give me some money.
妈 开门
Mom, open the door!
妈 开门 我需要支票
Mom, open the door. I need a check.
又要来一次吗
Are we really doing this again?
我还是会撤销的
I'm just gonna cancel it anyway.
不行 你不能撤销支票
No, you won't. You won't cancel the check.
我当然会撤销支票
Of course I'm gonna cancel the check.
-不 你这次不能撤销 妈-里面什么都没了
- No, you won't cancel it this time, Mom.- There's nothing in there.
全都被你掏空了
You've taken it all.
我不得不去求你父亲给钱才能把农场保住
I have to beg your fatherfor money just to keep the farm.
你到底是有什么问题
What the fuck is wrong with you?
宝贝 你受伤了吗
Honey, are you hurt?
莱恩
Ryan!
什么
What?
莱恩 把狗带走 放进我车后面
Ryan, get the dog and put himin the back of my car!
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我要带走库珀
I'm gonna take Cooper.
我要把它带到很远的地方让它找不到回家的路
I'm gonna drive him so far away thathe will not be able to find his way home,
它会饿死 甚至更糟
and he's gonna starve or worse.
给我开一张支票 妈
Give me a check, Mom.
莱恩
Ryan!
莱恩 你找到库珀了吗
Ryan, did you get Cooper?
我在努力呢
I'm trying!
找到它 把它放到车后面
Just find him and put himin the back of the fucking car!
库珀
Cooper!
我不知道它跑哪去了
I don't know where the hell he is!
莱恩 快点
Ryan, well, hurry up!
库珀
Cooper!
妈 你到底什么毛病
What the fuck is the matter with you, Mom?
-把那臭狗给我-不
- Give me the fucking dog.- No! No!
把臭狗给我 妈
Give me the fucking dog, Mom.
-不-把
- No!- Give me the…
你是想我把你恶心的头发都拔掉吗
Do you want me to pull all yourfucking disgusting hair out?
嘿
Hey!
-走吧-莱恩 别碰我
- Let's go.- Get the fuck off of me, Ryan!
别碰我 别碰我
Get the fuck off of me! Get the fuck off of me!
你没有朋友 爸恨你
You got no friends, Dad fucking hates you,
你知道除了我以外 所有人都恨你吗
do you know everybodyfucking hates you except for me?
该死的
Fuck.
克莱尔 我们走吧
Claire, let's go.
来吧 我们走
Come on. We gotta go.
莱斯
Les?
瞧谁来了
Well,
你好啊
hello.
嗨
Hey.
你来了
There you are.
你气色真好
You look great.
见到你真开心
You're a sight for sore eyes.
-太久没见了-嗨
- It's been too long.- Hi.
所以是什么风把你吹来了
So what brings you down here anyway?
我去德比牧场给奈利歌德查克送一辆拖车
I had to drop a trailer off atNelly Godschalk's at Derby Ranch.
奈利最近怎么样
How is Nelly these days?
噢 老天 她还是那么贱
Oh, God, she's still an awful old cunt.
每次离开的时候我都想对着她的脸来一拳
Every time I leave, I just wannapunch her straight in the face.
我好久没见她了
I haven't seen her in so long.
我是说
I mean,
我其实好久没见任何人了
haven't seen anybody really.
你没错过什么精彩的 相信我
Well, you're not missing much. Trust me.
现在谁帮你打理农场
So who's helping youtake care of the place?
没人 没人
No one. No one.
没人
No one?
天 凯特 你疯了吗
God, Kate, are you out of your mind?
从来都只有我和帕蒂 你也知道的
It was always just me and Patty, you know.
你感觉还好吗
How you holding up?
怎么说呢
I mean…
感谢老天 我还得照顾马
Thank God I havethe horses to take care of,
否则我早上都不想起床
otherwise I wouldn't getout of bed in the morning.
才过了九个月而已
It's only been nine months…
一切太突然了
and it was so sudden.
对 是的 是啊
Yeah, it was. Yeah.
只是
It was just…
我没法和任何人聊她 你知道吗
I can't really talk about herwith anybody, you know?
-你可以随时找我的 你知道的-我不想打扰你
- You can always call me, you know that.- I don't wanna bother you.
-我不想 -你绝对不会打扰我
- I don't wanna--- You are never a bother.
谢谢
Thanks.
不如我今天留下来帮你打理一下农场 在这过夜
Why don't I just stay and help out on thefarm today, and then I can stay the night?
你自己也有事要忙 你自己也有事要忙
You've got your own stuff to take care of. You've got your own stuff to take care of.
噢 少来
Oh, shut up.
琼恩的母亲正住在我们家
Joan's mother's staying.
我巴不得找个机会喘口气呢
God knows I could use a vacation from her.
我们可以做晚餐
We can make dinner,
不知道 醉得稀巴烂
I don't know, get drunk as skunks
然后笑得前仰后合 像以前一样
and laugh our tits offjust like old times.
好
Okay.
好的
好了
All right.
你又开始教马术课了
So you're teaching riding lessons again?
我是想的
Trying to.
最近在联络老客户
I've been calling my old clients.
是 和新的一样好
Yes, as good as new.
我毁了自己的家庭
I broke up our family.
是我爱上了“拉拉牧场工”
I'm the one who fell in lovewith the "lesbo ranch hand,"
正如理查德爱说的那样
as Richard liked to tell people.
-是-好了 我一会儿就点外卖
- Yeah.- All right, I'll order some takeout soon.
我吃什么都行 除了纯素火鸡
Order me anything, except vegan turkey.
噢 天啊
Oh, my God.
你还记得那次帕蒂用银餐盘装纯素火鸡吗
Do you remember the time Pattyserved it on a silver platter?
她好自豪
She was so proud of that.
老天爷 那味道就像一堆屁眼
Christ. I mean,it tasted like a thousand assholes.
是啊
Yeah.
克莱尔呢
And what about Claire?
我们上次聊的时候 她回去戒毒了 我们上次聊的时候 她回去戒毒了
The last time we talked,she was back in rehab. The last time we talked,she was back in rehab.
是 她又逃走了
Yeah, she skipped out again.
天啊
Jesus.
我一直觉得我这么乏味的人不会有这样乱糟糟的人生
I always thought I was too boringfor my life to be this messed up.
你的人生没有乱糟糟
Your life is not a mess.
你还在哀悼中 你失去了帕蒂
You're grieving, you lost Patty.
这种事没有标准做法可照搬
I mean, there's no road map for that shit.
要命
Fuck me.
这话简直是贺曼卡片上的话
That's the Hallmark card.
“哀悼
"Grief.
这种事没有标准做法可照搬”
There is no road map for that shit."
该死 是啊
Fuck. Yeah.
好了 我们休息吧
Now… Okay, let's get a little rest here.
-好 我想休息-好的
- Okay, I wanna rest.- Now, okay…
一步一个脚印
One foot in front of the other.
慢慢来
Easy.
瞧吧 我们还能跳舞
You see? We can still dance.
舞池已经打烊
Dance floor is closed.
该死
Fuck.
天啊
My God.
-那是我的袜子-对
- That's my sock.- Yeah, yeah.
-我要睡了-好了
- I gotta go to bed.- Here you go.
我走了
I gotta go.
好 谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
好了
There you are.
莱斯
Les?
（你的舞技还是很烂 爱你随时打给我 L）
（帕蒂）
嘿 亲爱的我找到克莱尔了 让她冷静下来了
Hey, sweetheart.I found Claire and calmed her down.
她觉得很愧疚
She feels terrible about what happened.
我们会快快地吃个饭 然后我送她回家
We're gonna grab a quick bite,and I'll bring her home.
这暴雪太吓人了
This snowstorm is crazy.
路上的雪太厚了我们可能要过很久才到家
There is so much snow on the road,so it's going to take us a while.
你休息吧
Get some rest.
外侧的控制再加强一些
A little more outside connection.
-很好-直起身子 玛尔
- Good.- Straighten up, Mal.
老天 你样子就像钟楼怪人 老天 你样子就像钟楼怪人
For fuck's sake,you look like Quasimodo out there. For fuck's sake,you look like Quasimodo out there.
艾玛 能麻烦你别打扰吗
Emma, do you mind?
妈 她才说我骑得很好
Mom, she literally just saidI was doing good.
用一下你身体里的骨头好吗
Use any of the bone structure you have…
-天啊 你能消停一会儿吗 -把上身挺起来
- God, can you stop for one minute?- …to keep yourself upright.
慢慢来 稳住
Nice and easy.
你来这做什么
What are you doing here?
我需要帮助
I need help.
好的
Okay.
好 我们先把外套脱了
Okay. Okay. Let's get this off of you.
你在流血吗
Are you bleeding?
没有 对不起 妈妈
I'm not. I'm sorry, Mom.
是莱恩的血
It's Ryan's.
好的
Okay.
好的 冷静冷静 深呼吸
Okay, calm down. Breathe.
我们去露营 然后又吵起来了
We went camping,and we started arguing again.
我发誓我不知道包里有什么 妈
And I promise I didn't knowwhat was in the bag, Mom.
-我不知道里面有什么-我知道 我相信你
- I didn't know what was inside.- I know. I believe you.
我推了他一把 我推了他一把
I pushed him. I pushed him.
我没想到会推得那么大力的 妈
I didn't mean to do it so hard, Mom.
然后他倒在斜坡上 撞到头 就
And then he fell over the slope,and he hit his head and it just…
撞开了
Just opened up.
宝贝 什么撞开了 什
What opened up, honey? What--
他的脑袋 就
His head, it just…
到处都是血 妈妈
There was just blood everywhere, Mom.
它就
Just…
他人还好吗
Is he okay?
你报警了吗
Did you call the police?
-没有-为什么
- No.- Why?
那是个意外 是
It was an accident. It was…
他 你们在吵架 他摔倒了 撞到脑袋
He… You were arguingand he fell, and he hit his head.
这不是犯罪
That's not a crime.
-没有理由不报 -不 他没有摔倒 妈 不是
- There's no reason to not call the--- No. He didn't fall, Mom. No.
是我用石头砸的他
I hit him with a rock.
他当时很生气 我怕了
He was getting so angry, and I got scared
他朝我扑来 我就 我 妈 他朝我扑来 我就 我 妈
and he was coming at me and I just…I… Mom. and he was coming at me and I just…I… Mom.
妈 怎么办 我们该
Mom, what do we do? What do we…
我们该
What do we…
莱恩现在在哪
Where is Ryan now?
我会问你一些问题
I'm gonna ask you some questions,
你必须对我实话实说 好吗
and you need to becompletely honest with me, okay?
你们去了哪里
Where did you go?
弗吉谷
Valley Forge.
我们
We just…
我们停下车 选了一个地方
We just parked and picked a spot.
你们登记了吗
Did you check in?
有没有登记站
I mean, was there a check-in station?
没有 不是那种
No, it wasn't anything like that.
我们就停在街道的一侧 然后
We just parked on the sideof the street and then we…
我们走进树林深处
We just walked deep into the woods.
有人见到你们吗
Did anyone see you?
没有
No.
没有人看到你们停车树林里也没有人看到你们
No one saw you park,and no one saw you in the woods?
对 我们就
Yeah, we just…
-我们就停车 然后 -克莱尔 这很重要
- We just parked and--- Claire, it's important.
不 妈 我是说
No, Mom. I mean…
天 我觉得没有人看到我们 妈
God, I don't think they did, Mom.
我们第一晚到的时候已经很晚了 第二天
We got there so late the first nightand then the next day,
我们去周围走了走 也许有人见到我们
we went for a walk,so maybe people could have seen us
-在水边见到 有可能-是 好的
- down by the water, I guess.- Yeah. Okay.
是
Yeah.
莱恩的手机在你这里吗
Do you have Ryan's cell phone?
有谁知道你们去过哪里吗
Does anyone knowwhere the two of you were?
没有
No.
好的 你上楼把衣服都脱了 放进一个袋子
Okay, go upstairs, take offall your clothes, and put them in a bag
别离开你的卧室 等我回来
and don't leave your bedroomtill I come back.
你要去哪里
Come back from where?
照我说的做就好
Just do what I say.
（欢迎来到玛什溪湖）
走吧
Let's go.
你去做什么了
What'd you do?
我处理好了
I took care of it.
全都处理了
All of it.
你能陪我一会儿吗
Will you stay with me for a little bit?
我们得先把一些细节对一对 我们得先把一些细节对一对
We need to go through a few things We need to go through a few things
好统一口径 以免有人问
so that we're on the same page,in case anyone asks.
这样 你们俩露营后回到这里
So, the two of youcame back here after camping,
你们吵了一架 我也在场 然后莱恩走了
you got into an argument,I witnessed it, and then Ryan left.
等等 为什么要说莱恩来过这里 那不会
Wait. Why would we sayRyan was here? Would we not--
因为你把他的手机带回来了
Because you broughthis cell phone back here,
如果警察检查手机记录就会知道他来过这里
and if the police check phone records,they'll know that he was here.
所以这就是我们的说法
So that's our story.
你们两人露营后回来 吵了一架
The two of you came back here aftercamping, you got into an argument,
我在场 然后莱恩走了你留下 整晚都和我在一起
I witnessed it, and then Ryan left, andthen you stayed here with me all night.
他在哪里
Where is he?
玛什溪湖
Marsh Creek Lake.
湖里 为什么
The lake? Why the lake?
因为天很晚了 克莱尔 我觉得
Because it was late, Claire,and I didn't think
-我没时间埋他 -天啊
- that I would have time to bury him--- Oh, my God.
-天啊 妈-那
- Oh, my God. Mom.- It's…
克莱尔 我需要你坚强起来
Claire, you have to be strong for me.
-你能做到吗 -天啊
- Can you do that?- Oh, my God.
-别 不要这么说了 妈-必须这样 你
- Stop. Stop saying that, Mom.- You have to. You--
我没有要求你做任何事 我没让你去
I didn't ask you to do anything.I didn't tell you to go…
我不需要你告诉我我这么做是因为我爱你 我不需要你告诉我我这么做是因为我爱你
You didn't have to tell me.I did it because I love you. You didn't have to tell me.I did it because I love you.
我爱你 克莱尔 我不会让你出事
I love you, Claire,and I won't let anything happen to you.
怎么了
What's wrong?
杰基
Jackie.
哪个杰基
Jackie who?
之前来过的那个男人
The guy who was here before.
莱恩欠他钱
The one Ryan owes money to.
他跟踪我去商店 说要杀了我
He followed me to the store,and he said he was gonna fucking kill me.
他说了什么
What did he say?
他走到我跟前 用枪顶着我的下巴
He came up to meand he jammed a gun right under my chin.
-他说他会杀了我-好的 冷静一下 -他说他会杀了我-好的 冷静一下
- He said he's going to fucking kill me.- Okay. Calm down. - He said he's going to fucking kill me.- Okay. Calm down.
我现在很慌 因为他在问莱恩的下落
I'm freaking out right nowbecause he's asking about Ryan,
他问的人越多
and the more people he asks about Ryan,
越多人就会好奇他去哪了 然后
they're gonna start questioningwhere he is and…
莱恩欠了多少钱
How much money does Ryan owe?
一万
Ten thousand.
-尸体会浮上水面-什么
- Bodies float.- What?
我读过 尸体会浮上水面 尤其在
I read that bodies float,especially when it's…
天气热的时候 像现在
When it's hot out like it is right now.
肠胃里有一种细菌会生长 胸部会胀气
This bacteria grows in the gutand the chest fills with gas
然后尸体会浮到水面上
and then they float to the surface.
（凯特盖瑞特森 九千美元 理查德G.）
终于想通了
Finally came to your senses.
这是我女儿欠的数 一切到此为止 这是我女儿欠的数 一切到此为止
This is what my daughter owes,so it's the end of it. This is what my daughter owes,so it's the end of it.
现在轮到你定规则了
You're making the rules now?
啊 老妈
Huh, Mom?
很好
Nice.
你在这里教课
You give lessons out here?
马术课
Horse lessons?
我一直都想骑马最近刚好有些闲钱 所以
I always wanted to ride a horse, and Ijust recently came into some money, so…
我再也不想看到你出现在这里
I never wanna see youon this property ever again.
听见了吗
You understand me?
一定很难受吧
It must be fucking awful.
什么
What?
生了个这样的孩子
Having a kid like that.
总是得帮她收拾烂摊子
Always having to clean up their shit.
结束了
It's over.
他不会再来烦我们了
He won't bother us anymore.
起来吧 吃早餐了
Let's get up. Time for breakfast.
嗨 我是克莱尔
Hey. This is Claire's phone.
给我发短信吧
Just text me instead.
嗨 是我
Hey. It's me.
只是想看看你在哪 只是想看看你在哪
I'm just checking to see where you are. I'm just checking to see where you are.
打给我
Call me.
换边起落
Change your diagonal.
很不错
Good job.
非常好
Excellent.
保持呼吸节奏
Keep breathing.
（克莱尔 请打给我 克莱尔）
能用一下你的iPad吗 我想登入账户查短信
Can I have your iPad so I can log inand check my messages?
（查找）
（克莱尔的iPhone 94公里）
（伦波街公园）
嘿 我不懂你怎么能光坐着
Hey, I don't understandhow you can sit there
整天看电视
and fucking watch TV all day.
我就想整天看电视
I wanna fucking watch TV all day.
你老妈在外面
Your fucking mom is outside.
什么
What?
克莱尔
Claire.
克莱尔 开门
Claire, open the door.
快点 从沙发上下来 我们走
Let's go. Get off the fucking couch.Let's go.
-克莱尔 开门-她知道了
- Claire. Open the door.- She fucking knows.
-怎么回事 -我们得走了
- What's going on?- Let's fucking go.
-拿上你的东西-喂
- Get your fucking shit.- Come on.
-莱恩-从后面出去 快点
- Ryan!- Out the back. Come on.
开门
Open it!
-克莱尔-快走
- Claire.- Let's go.
该死
Fuck!
等等
Come on.
克莱尔 下车
Claire, get out of the car.
下车 跟我说话
Get out of the car and talk to me.
那具尸体是谁的
Whose body was that?
-关门-关不上
- Close the door!- I can't!
告诉我你对我做了什么
Tell me what you did to me.
克莱尔 别这样 下车
Claire. Come on. Get out.
-莱恩 不要-滚开 -莱恩 不要-滚开
- Ryan! No!- Fuck off! - Ryan! No!- Fuck off!
烦死了
For fuck's sake.
克莱尔 请开门
Claire, please open the door.
求求你
Please.
（Apple ID 克莱尔盖瑞特森）
（莱恩 宝贝 我压力好大）
（我也是 我好不舒服）
（她刚出门 奏效了 事成了）
（我不敢相信她去做了）
（我能让她做任何事）
（删除）
（玛什溪湖深度）
提醒一下 如果超出了两小时
Just so you know,if you end up going over the two hours,
那就按一天来计费
we're gonna have to charge youfor the whole day.
-是 两小时够了-好的
- Yeah. Two hours will be fine.- Okay.
-这一艘可以吗 -可以 谢谢你
- Is this one good?- Yeah. Thank you.
-下午好-嘿 嗨
- Afternoon.- Hey. Hi.
-你在这里做什么 -没什么
- What are you doing out here?- I'm not doing much of anything.
来游泳 怎么了
Just swimming. Why?
湖滩上的女孩说你已经超时了
Girl on the beach there saidyou'd gone over your time.
-她有点担心你-噢 我没事
- She was worried about you.- Oh, no.
我是说 我
I mean, I…
我的结婚戒指不见了
I lost my wedding ring,
我想找一找
and I thought I would try to find it.
感觉有点蠢
It seems pretty stupid.
以为能在这个大湖里找到
Thought I could find it in this big lake.
你想听个有意思的事吗
You wanna hear something funny?
好啊
Okay.
我在蜜月期间弄丢了戒指
I lost my ring on our honeymoon.
在礁岛群的海里
Down in the Keys.
我妻子差点掐死我
My wife was ready to strangle me.
听着 我和你说个好消息 也许算坏消息
Look, here's the good, or bad news.
你的婚姻还在 不是吗
You're still married, right?
对
Yeah.
今天就到此为止吧
Maybe call it a day, huh?
过去 我所以为的爱其实都只是一种模仿
Everything I thoughtabout love was just an imitation.
现在 我真的站在爱的亮光下我再也不想失去它
But now that I've stood in its light,I never wanna be without it.
好的 帕蒂 轮到你了
Okay, Patty. Your turn.
我尽力啊
Here goes nothing.
凯特 我的爱
Kate, my love.
我一辈子都在寻找一个家
I've spent my whole lifesearching for home.
家是心灵的港湾 避难的地方
Home is a place of comfort, refuge.
你就是我的家
You are my home.
今天最棒的一点在于 这只是我们的开始
And the best part of today isthat it's just the beginning for us.
你可以吻新娘了
And now you can kiss the bride.
（凯特与帕蒂 2018年3月3日）
（凯特来电）
天啊 现在是凌晨2点
Jesus Christ.It's two o'clock in the morning.
一切还好吗
Is everything all right?
不太好
Not really.
出了什么问题
What's wrong?
大问题
Everything.
嗨
Hi.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
你昨晚和我说的都是真的吗
Is everything you told me last night true?
是的
Yeah.
我的天啊
Jesus Christ.
好 你跟我去一趟维尔德维尔 好 你跟我去一趟维尔德维尔
Yeah, you're coming with me to Wildvale. Yeah, you're coming with me to Wildvale.
我不能把马自己留在家里 所以
I can't leave the horses, so…
我全都打点好了
I've taken care of everything.
丹妮斯邓曼牧场的两个朋友会开车过来
Two friends from Denise Denman'sranch are driving down.
他们30分钟后到
They're gonna be here in 30 minutes.
你必须休息几天 然后我们会想办法处理
You need to rest for a few daysand then we'll figure this out.
凯特 收拾行李
Kate, get packed.
有什么有趣的
Anything interesting…
到了
We're here.
嗨 嗨
Hi. Hi.
啊 亲爱的
Aw, sweetie.
莱斯说你最近很不顺
Les told me that you're going through it.
是 有点 对
Yeah, a little bit. Yeah.
我给你泡了点茶
I made you some tea.
麻烦你了
Thank you.
给
Here.
-你知道路的-好
- You know the way.- Okay.
没事 给我吧 对
No, I got it. I got it. Yeah.
好的
All right.
她打给你母亲了
She called your mother?
-天啊 她说了什么 -是啊
- Oh, God. What did she say?- Damn right.
“我们在谷仓找到了莱斯和另一名女性
"We found Lesand another female in the barn.
她们在做一些事”
They were doing things to each other."
“什么样的事 ” 我母亲问
"What kind of things?" my mother said.
“我们听到了有性意味的呻吟声” “我们听到了有性意味的呻吟声”
"Well, we heard moaningof a sexual nature." "Well, we heard moaningof a sexual nature."
“噢” 我母亲说
"Oh," it's my mother.
“真好 听起来她们在做一些正确的事”
"Wonderful. Sounds likethey were doing the right kind of things."
说得好
I love that.
这一杯敬格兰德森太太和她饱受折磨的丈夫
Cheers to Mrs. Grandersonand her long-suffering husband.
格兰德森老先生怎么样了
How is old Mr. Granderson?
他还经营那个漂亮的农场吗
Does he still have that beautiful farm?
他一把火把农场烧平了
The old man burned the place down.
烧平了 为什么
He burned it down? Why?
他被诊断患有阿兹海默症
He got diagnosed with Alzheimer's.
他不希望孩子被迫提供长期照护
He didn't want his kids to be on the hookfor long-term care,
所以有天晚上 他放火烧了草棚想假装成事故
so he set fire to the hayloft one night,trying to make it look like an accident
好领保险赔款
so he'd collect the insurance payout.
但被警察发现了
But the police caught him.
-谁要添杯 凯特 -我要 给我加一点
- Who's for a top-up? Kate?- Yep. Yeah, I'll have a little.
不 你不行
No. No, no. Not you.
看来我明早得自己干活了
Looks like I'll be doingthe chores myself tomorrow morning.
谢谢
Thank you.
-好了 -是 天
- Ready?- Yeah, God.
-干杯-干杯
- Cheers.- Cheers.
（门铃摄像头）
有人吗
Hello.
你来我家做什么
What are you doing at my house?
出来
Come on out.
我不在家
I'm not home right now.
离家好几小时车程
I'm hours away.
那你应该回家
Well, you should get home.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
谈什么
About what?
谈你抛到玛什溪湖的尸体
About the body you dumpedat Marsh Creek Lake.
你还在吗
You still there?
在
Yeah.
你现在觉得我们应该谈谈了吧
You think it's importantthat we talk now, right?
我明天回家
I'll be home tomorrow.
中午
Noon.
进来吧
Come in.
嗨
Hey.
那人是谁
Who was it?
某人的表弟
Someone's cousin.
某人的哥哥
Someone's brother.
某人的孩子
Someone's child.
-别和我绕圈子了 给我名字-某人的小孩
- Stop fucking around. I want a name.- Someone's kid.
-我想知道那是谁-别管了
- I wanna know who it was.- Forget who it was.
现在重要的是
What's important right now
你要明白自己的处境多么惨
is that you understandjust how utterly fucked you are.
很好
Good.
好了
All right.
莱恩欠我一万块也就是你女儿扔掉的毒品
So, Ryan owed me ten grandfor the drugs your daughter tossed,
他又开始卖货了 想要把钱赚回来
and he starts dealing,trying to earn it back.
但他心太急 在毒品里混了芬太尼充数
But he gets impatient and he cutsthe drugs with fentanyl to stretch it,
那也没什么 但他人蠢 所以做得太过了 那也没什么 但他人蠢 所以做得太过了
and that's fine but he pushes ittoo far 'cause he's dumb. and that's fine but he pushes ittoo far 'cause he's dumb.
有个小孩吸莱恩卖给他的毒品时过量死了
And this kid OD'son the drugs that Ryan sold him.
莱恩和克莱尔找到我 他们吓得屁滚尿流
And Ryan and Claire come to meand they're freaking the fuck out,
所以我让他们冷静下来帮他们想了个办法
and so I calm them both down,and I come up with a plan.
不得不说 我其实没想到
And I gotta be honest. I did not think
你还真的会上钩
that you were gonna fuckingactually do it,
但克莱尔说你会做的因为你对她有无条件的爱
but Claire said that you wouldon account of your unconditional love.
她说得没错
And she was right.
你抛尸 还了钱 于是到了现在的局面
You dumped the body,you got my money, and here we are.
克莱尔知道你过来吗
Does Claire know you're doing this?
她知道
She does.
不 说笑的 她不知道
No. She doesn't.
我只是看到了一个难得的机会
I'm seizing an opportunity.
你已经走到这一步了我猜你不介意更进一步 对吧
You've gone this far. I figureyou'll go a little farther, right?
所以 你想要什么
So what do you want?
出了一些事 我必须离开一阵 我希望
Some things have come up, and I need toleave town for a while, and I would like
-在走前拿到我的钱-我已经把钱还你了
- to get paid out before I go.- I already paid you.
你给了我一万块 你给了我一万块
You paid me ten fucking grand. You paid me ten fucking grand.
那不够 你还没明白现在的情况
I want more.Do you not see what's going on here?
我比你领先无数步 女士
I'm light-years ahead of you, lady.
现在 没有人在搜寻某个失踪的毒虫
Right now, no one's searching forsome fucking missing dope addict
以后也不会有 但我打一宗匿名电话
and no one ever will,but I make one anonymous call,
突然之间 他们就会开始把那湖搜个底朝天
and all of a sudden,they're dragging the bottom of that lake,
然后展开调查
and then there's an investigation
所有线索都指向莱恩 克莱尔和你
and all roads lead backto Ryan and Claire and to you.
你完了
You're fucked.
我没有钱
I don't have any money.
-我现在手头 -别说这种话 别说什么
- I am having a hard time…- Don't fucking say that to me. Don't say
-你没钱的屁话-我连
- you don't have any fucking money.- …I'm having trouble just making…
-闭嘴吧 闭嘴-生活费都没有
- Fucking shut up. Shut up.- …the bills.
你在切斯特县有大片土地
You have acres and acres of landin Chester fucking County.
你有马 有谷仓 还有一个大房子
You have horses and barnsand a fucking house,
别坐在这儿和我哭穷
so don't fucking sit there and tell methat you have nothing
因为你很有钱 而我要分一杯羹
'cause you have a lot, and I want it.
我不谈了
I can't do this.
过来
Come here. Come here.
不 放开我
No. Get off!
-放开我-不 -放开我-不
- Get off me!- No! - Get off me!- No!
放开我
Get off!
-放开我 -别动
- Get off! Get off!- Stop.
别动
Stop, stop, stop.
不要
No, no.
不
No.
-不要 -看着我
- No, no. No.- Look at me. Look at me.
好
Okay.
这就对了
There we go.
你没事
You're okay.
你很好
You're all right.
你没事的
You're okay.
起床啦 天 起来
Wakey-wakey. Jesus Christ. Get up.
搞什么 我给你注射了200毫克而已你就变成睡美人了
Fuck. I gave you 200 milligrams,and you're acting like Sleeping Beauty.
起来了
Let's go.
来吧
Come on.
好 我拿走了你的手机电脑 车钥匙和房门钥匙
All right, so I took your phone, computer,car keys, house keys.
没有我的允许你不能离开这个农场 明白吗
You don't leave this propertywithout my permission. You understand?
给你两天时间付我钱
You got two days to pay me.
我睡在哪儿
Where am I sleeping?
有人住在这里吗
Someone live here?
我妻子在我们交往前住在这里
My wife did before we got together.
她发生了什么
What happened to her?
她死了
She died.
拖拉机回火 马受惊把她摔下去了她摔断了脖子 拖拉机回火 马受惊把她摔下去了她摔断了脖子
Tractor backfired, her horse threw her,and she broke her neck. Tractor backfired, her horse threw her,and she broke her neck.
真惨
That sucks.
嘿 我不希望任何人过来这里只能有你和我
Hey. I don't want anyonehanging around here except me and you.
写个你客户的名单
Make a list of your clients.
我会发短信说你无法教课
I'll send out a text sayingyou're not available for lessons.
你不吃吗
You're not gonna eat?
我没什么胃口
I don't have much of an appetite.
嘿
Hey.
请别给它喂那个
Please don't feed him that.
它挺喜欢的
He likes it.
你看它
Look at him.
你会害它生病的
You'll make him sick.
该死
Shit.
（克莱尔 对不起）
（克莱尔 忘了我吧）
（我真希望自己死了）
（他叫格雷戈卡敏斯基）
（格雷戈卡敏斯基）
天啊
Oh, God.
天啊 我打你手机50次了
Jesus Christ.I must have called you 50 fucking times.
你是想让我心脏病发吗
Are you trying to give me a heart attack?
嘿 老格兰德森的谷仓火灾那次他是怎么被发现的
Hey. Old Granderson's barn fire,how did he get caught?
-什么 -他被逮捕了 为什么
- What?- He was arrested. Why?
我不喜欢你现在的思路
I don't likewhere your head's at right now.
莱斯 拜托 告诉我 求求你
Les, come on. Just tell me, please.
他用了一个燃烧棒
He used a flare.
他事先研究过 我猜他发现
He'd researched it,and I guess he found out
用燃烧棒引火基本不会被发现
that starting a fire with a flarewould be virtually undetectable.
但他被逮捕了
But he was arrested.
因为他落下了一个东西燃烧棒的某个部件
Because he left something behind.A part of the flare.
我不记得具体是什么了
I don't remember exactly what,
但消防员发现的时候就知道是有人故意点火的
but when the fire marshal found it,he knew it was set intentionally.
所以你为什么想知道这个 所以你为什么想知道这个
Why do you wanna know all this anyway? Why do you wanna know all this anyway?
凯特 你真的没事吗
Kate, are you sure you're okay?
我很快会打给你的
I'll call you back soon, okay?
这是粮仓的保险 价值十万美元
That's $100,000 of insurance on the barn.
如果粮仓失火的话
If you burn it.
没错
Right.
要怎么做到而不被任何人发现
How exactly do you do thatwithout these guys knowing you did it?
干草在130度时会自燃
Hay spontaneously combusts at 130 degrees.
这常常会发生但如果用燃烧棒 那就不会被发现
It happens all the time, but if you usea flare, then it's undetectable.
谷仓烧了后要等多久 我才能拿到钱
How long after you burn itwill it take for me to get my money?
不知道 几周到一个月吧
I don't know.I mean, a couple weeks or a month.
那不行
No. No.
想其他办法
Figure out a different plan.
我只有这个办法
This is what I have.
我考虑过了
I've thought about this.
我非常仔细 周全地考虑过 我向你保证
I've thought about it really carefully,and I promise you
-这样你一定能拿到钱-怎么拿到 -这样你一定能拿到钱-怎么拿到
- that you can get your money this way.- How? - that you can get your money this way.- How?
理赔到账时 我已经在美国另一边了
I will be clear across the countryby the time that payout arrives.
我可以雇你为农场的员工然后把钱分期转给你
I could make you an employee of the farm,and then send it in installments,
这样就不会引人注意
and then I don't thinkit'll get flagged that way.
马呢
What about the horses?
马怎么了
What about them?
也买了保险吗
Are they insured too?
买了 但是 这是寄养所
Yeah, but this is a boarding facility,
所以不是所有马都属于我
so not all of the horses belong to me.
多少匹是你的
How many do?
两匹
Two.
那两匹的保险理赔是多少
How much are those two insured for?
每匹两万五千
25,000 each.
那就一起烧了
So we burn them too.
这样赔款就涨到十五万
And that brings the payout to 150,000.
-但如果我们 -那很好
- But if we--- That's good.
-但如果我们把我的马也烧了 -你是蠢吗
- But if we just burn my horses--- What, are you fucking stupid?
我们不会只烧你的马 所有马都要烧死
We're not just gonna burn your horses.We burn all the horses.
用用脑子
Use your head.
-谁来了 -是艾玛
- Who's that?- That's Emma.
一个客户
She's a client.
她怎么会来 我以为已经取消她的课了
What's she doing here?I thought we canceled her lesson.
是取消了 我去招呼她
We did. I'll get it.
不 你留在这里
No, no. You stay here.
下午好
Afternoon.
你是艾玛 对吗
It's Emma, right?
凯特呢
Where's Kate?
她醒来发现发烧了
She woke up with a fever.
别担心 我会好好照顾她的
Don't worry.I'm taking real good care of her.
不好意思 你是哪位
I'm sorry. Who are you exactly?
我是新来的农场工 我是新来的农场工
I'm the new fucking farmhand. I'm the new fucking farmhand.
几天前刚开始来干活的
Just started a few days ago.
好吧 我只需要拿几块马鞍垫在纽黑文的表演秀上用的
Okay. I'm just gonna grab some ofthese saddle pads for the New Haven show.
-我帮你吧-不 没事 不用你帮忙了
- Let me help.- No. I'm fine. I don't need any help.
我来就好
I got it.
我说了不用你帮忙
I said I don't need your help.
好吧
All right.
意思是你可以走了
That means you can go.
你能给我一点空间吗
Can you get out of my space?
艾玛是个贱人
Emma's a fucking bitch.
好 我们就烧了它
Okay. We'll burn it.
但由你动手
But it's on you.
全部都由你来
All of it.
因为如果事情败露 那我要甩得一干二净
'Cause if shit goes sideways,I'm nowhere near any of this.
嘿 戴尔 麻烦你了 临时帮我送来
Hey, Dale. Appreciate youfitting me in on such short notice.
别客气
Yeah, you got it.
好了吗
Is it ready?
好了 我们在凌晨2点至3点期间点火
Yeah. We'll do itbetween 2:00 and 3:00 a.m.
让它烧一阵子
Let it burn for a while.
有人注意到并打给消防局时就已经太晚了 有人注意到并打给消防局时就已经太晚了
By the time anybody notices and callsthe fire department, it'll be too late. By the time anybody notices and callsthe fire department, it'll be too late.
很好
Cool.
嗨 帅哥
Hey, handsome.
我知道
I know.
一切都会好好的
Everything's gonna be okay.
我知道
I know.
你该走了
You should probably go now.
我觉得我还是留下吧
You know, I think I'm gonna stick around.
确保你把事做好了
Make sure you go through with it.
-你感觉如何 还好吗 -不太好
- How you doing? You doing okay?- Not really. No.
消防员刚才告诉我
The fire marshal just informed me
是有人故意放火的 盖瑞特森太太
that the blaze was set intentionally,Ms. Garretson.
这是一个钢丝支架 常用于道路燃烧棒
It's a wire stand.They're commonly used in road flares.
他是在着火点发现的
He found that at the point of ignition.
什么意思 你认为我
What are you saying? You think that I did…
你提过 粮仓上面的公寓里住过人
You mentioned there was someoneliving in the apartment above the barn.
一个员工 杰基罗森
An employee. Jackie Lawson.
杰基昨晚在家吗 他在公寓里吗
Was Jackie home last night?Was he in the apartment?
我准备睡觉时
His car was there
-他的车还在-那是几点 -他的车还在-那是几点
- when I went to bed.- What time was that? - when I went to bed.- What time was that?
-你准备睡觉的时间-晚上10点吧 应该是
- When you went to bed.- Like 10 p.m. probably.
所以你注意到外面起火时
So when you noticed the fire outside,
你记得杰基的车还在吗
do you rememberif Jackie's car was still there?
不在 我今天早上打给他想告诉他发生了什么
It wasn't. And I called him this morningto let him know what was going on,
但我没有他的消息
but I haven't heard anything from him.
盖瑞特森太太我们发现公寓里有一具死尸
Ms. Garretson,we found a dead body inside the apartment.
你觉得是杰基吗
Do you think it was Jackie?
我们不知道
We don't know.
你也能猜到 尸体被烧得非常严重
As you could imagine,it was very badly burned.
我需要你和我去一趟警局
I need you to come downto the station with me.
好 抱歉让你久等了
Okay. Sorry for the wait.
好消息是 我们确认找到杰基了
Good news iswe were able to locate Jackie.
噢 感谢老天
Oh, thank God.
盖瑞特森太太 你们是怎么认识的
How'd you two meet, Ms. Garretson?
我和杰基吗 是因为我女儿克莱尔他是她的朋友
Jackie and I? Through my daughter, Claire.He's a friend of hers.
他在找工作我刚好需要找人帮我打理马厩
He was looking for a job, and I neededsomebody to help me out in the stables.
那奇怪了 杰基声称他从没帮你打过工
It's odd 'cause Jackie claimshe never worked for you.
说他从没在那个公寓里住过事实上 他说他都不知道你是谁
Never lived in the apartment. In fact,he says he doesn't even know who you are.
他不知道我是谁
He doesn't know who I am?
可他
But he's…
他一直住在农场 在那儿工作
He's been livingon the farm and working there.
他为什么会说不认识我 他为什么会说不认识我
Why would he saythat he doesn't know who I am? Why would he saythat he doesn't know who I am?
你的客户呢
What about clients?
他们应该在农场见过他的
I'd imagine they'd have seen himhanging around the place.
我取消了所有课程
I canceled all my lessons.
我妻子最近过世了
My wife passed away recently.
我没能恢复正常生活
I've had a really hard timegetting back on my feet.
请节哀
I'm sorry.
-艾玛汉威-什么
- Emma Hanway.- What's that?
艾玛汉威是一个客户
Emma Hanway is a client.
我曾发短信让她来拿一个马鞍垫
I texted her to pick up a saddle pad.
你 我可以把她的联络方式给你
I mean, you… I could give her your contact
-如果有用的话-请给我吧
- if you think that would be helpful.- Please.
你有注意到杰基和谁在一起吗
Was there anyone with Jackiethat you noticed?
有谁来找过他 可能进过公寓
Anyone hanging around?Going inside the apartment?
我没有特别关注他在做什么
I mean, I didn't keep a really…a close watch on him.
但是有一个人 但是有一个人
There was one person though. There was one person though.
他曾向我介绍自己
He introduced himself to me once.
-格雷戈-格
- Greg.- G…
卡米斯基 卡敏斯基 好像叫这个
Kamiski. Kaminski. Something like that.
你认得他吗
You recognize him?
不
Nope.
他叫格雷戈卡敏斯基
His name is Greg Kaminski.
验尸官刚通过牙科报告确认了身份
Medical examiner just confirmed itthrough dental records.
好的
Okay.
他的尸体今天早上在回音谷被发现
His body was found outat Echo Valley this morning.
在粮仓上方的公寓里
Inside that apartment above the barn.
好吧 我已经告诉你了我没有在那个农场住过
All right. Well, I already told youI wasn't staying at that farm.
-我不知道这什么 -杰基 我知道
- I don't know this fucking--- Jackie, I know you been working
你在农场做工 我有银行对账单可以证明
on the farm.I got the bank statement to prove it.
银行对账单
Bank statement?
盖瑞特森太太向你的银行账户汇了两千五百美元
$2,500 wired to your bank accountfrom Ms. Garretson's.
此外 盖瑞特森太太的一位客户
In addition, a client of Ms. Garretson's
确认她曾在农场见过你 确认她曾在农场见过你
confirmed that she saw youat the property. confirmed that she saw youat the property.
好吧 我们倒回去讲
All right.Let's just fucking rewind, okay?
我们倒回去 从头说起
Let's rewind and just go from the top.
我会把整件事一五一十告诉你 好吗
I'm gonna tell you exactly what happened,all right?
我会告诉你到底发生了什么
I'm going to tell youwhat actually happened.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
我打你手机50次了你是想让我心脏病发吗
I must have called you 50 fucking times.Are you trying to give me a heart attack?
嘿 老格兰德森的谷仓火灾那次他是怎么被发现的
Hey. Old Granderson's barn fire,how did he get caught?
因为他落下了一个东西燃烧棒的某个部件
'Cause he left something behind.A part of the flare.
所以你为什么想知道这个
Why do you want to know all this anyway?
我很快会打给你的
I'll call you back soon, okay?
好
Okay.
（欢迎来到玛什溪湖）
就是这里 停下
There it is. Stop.
他走了
He's gone.
我们必须离开了
We gotta leave.
没事的
It's okay.
快走吧
Come on.
乖 快走
Good boy. Go, go!
你们被耍了
You guys are being played.
我们都在被她耍
We're all being fucking playedright now by her.
那么 我想确认一下
You know, just so I'm clear…
你的说法是 凯特的女儿
Your story is that Kate's daughter,
和她女儿的男朋友杀了格雷戈卡敏斯基
and her daughter's boyfriendkilled Greg Kaminski
然后让凯特去玛什溪湖抛尸
and had Kate dump the bodyat Marsh Creek Lake.
-我知道听起来不可思议-让我说完
- I know how it sounds.- I wasn't finished.
然后她用燃烧棒点火 而燃烧棒是你
Then she set the fire using flaresthat you purchased
在距离她农场1.6公里的速星加油站买的
from the Quick Star gas stationone mile from her farm.
你想知道我的看法吗
Do you wanna know what I think?
我认为格雷戈卡敏斯基是一个出了名的大毒虫
I think Greg Kaminski'sa known drug abuser.
我认为你是他的毒贩
I think you were his dealer.
我认为公寓里发生了一些事
I think something happenedinside the apartment.
-不 完全不对-我认为公寓里发生了
- No! Fucking no.- I think something happened inside--
-别把这件事怪到我身上-别激动 杰基
- Don't fucking pin this shit on me!- Relax, Jackie.
-别 -把手臂放下 坐下
- Don't fucking…- Put your arm down. Sit down.
你不明白 别碰我
You don't understand.Don't fucking touch me.
-退后-你别
- Get back there.- Don't you fucking…
-坐下-别碰我
- Sit down!- Don't fucking touch me.
别
Don't…
没事了
It's all right.
一切都结束了
It's all over now.
是 我听到了 滚吧 是 我听到了 滚吧
Yeah, yeah. I hear you, jerk off. Yeah, yeah. I hear you, jerk off.
-谢谢你-是
- Thank you.- Yeah.
-嗨 兰迪-嗨 凯特
- Hey, Randy.- Hey, Kate.
-你好吗 -还不错吧
- How's it going?- So far so good.
这周结束前会清理完毕
I'll have this cleanup doneby the end of the week.
如果运气好 冬天之前屋顶就能修好
Then with a little bit of luck,we'll be under roof before winter hits.
-太棒了 谢谢你-没事
- That's great. Thanks.- Yeah.
嘿 兰迪 发电机装好了
Hey, Randy. Generator's backed in.
我得去当保姆了
I gotta go play "Mom."
（克莱尔 你会原谅我吗 ）
（我真希望自己死了 你会原谅我吗 ）
好的 调整为工作快步
Okay, go to your working trot.
保持两点姿势 让它走步
Stay in two-point and ask him to walk.
稍微慢一点 稍微慢一点
Little slower. Little slower.
很好
There you go.
（帕蒂 手机）
嘿 是我
Hey, it's me.
我们在回家的路上了
We're on our way home now.
我告诉克莱尔 作为惩罚
I let Claire know that as a punishment,
她必须铲两个月的马粪
she'll be mucking horse shitfor the next two months.
-帕蒂 别这样-她想和你说一件事
- Stop, Patty.- She wants to tell you something.
嗨 妈 抱歉我总是在惹祸 嗨 妈 抱歉我总是在惹祸
Hi, Mom. I'm sorry for beingsuch a constant fuckup. Hi, Mom. I'm sorry for beingsuch a constant fuckup.
-嘿 这个话题已经过了-还有
- Hey. We're past that now.- And…
我爱你 你知道的
And I just love you, you know.
你听到了吗 她非常爱你 我也是
Did you hear that?She loves you like crazy and I do too.
雪变小了 我们很快会到家
The snow's eased upand we'll be home soon.